[{"answer": "Strange activity.  I think they running drugs off that place.  my friend don't believe me", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I know everything, playboy.  Don't hate, congratulate", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I went back to my friend to sell my old car and met her on the way.  Worst day of my life", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "That ain't the worst part.  Her little sister, Baby D.  She's the one that gets real physical.  But I got a restraining order on her, too", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Damn, you got a stalker", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You got a restraining order on a little girl named Baby D", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You want us to give you a ride", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What you mean, you don't know?  Just wait here", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Can I help you", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't play for no team", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Nice house. Didn't expect you to answer. You must be one of those entertainers. What team you play for", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Come on, jerky, you can tell me.  Got a white wife, huh?  Blonde bombshell type. Remember what happen to O.J... what team do you play for?  You're not related to the Jacksons, are you", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No, give me my damn money back.  Right now, and I don't have no damn receipt neither", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I don't have no damn cover", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I can't give you your damn money back on this", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Well, you gonna have to go postal then", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yeah, it was.  How you get up here", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You walked", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "D'Wana brought Baby'D up here", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You damn right that's the big one", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'm his cousin", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yeah, I work here now", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yeah, I work here now", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yes you did", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Just tell him to come over here and talk to me", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Go, fo' I change my mind", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What was what", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I didn't see no silver thing, and neither did you", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It is easy. You know why?  'Cause they're not expecting it. Now, my friend, you gotta occupy my friend. Long enough for me and my friend to take a good look", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Well get along with this one.  Go ahead of us.  Don't get seen and don't let that mutt out of your sight", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You go first", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You go first", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " No one's gonna hear that.  The music's playing", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "This is a knock", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Look, man, this is a big misunderstanding.  All we wanted to do is borrow some sugar", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "...and some rolling papers, that's it. We didn't mean to mess up y'all get together or nothing.  How y'all doing", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Ya'll live around here", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " Shhhh!  my friend, shut the fuck up", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Nothing.  What you want", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Take your car", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What you doing here", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Looks like a dead man", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "When my back gets better I'mma beat the black off you, my friend", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Sorry, my ass", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I threw my back, again", "docId": "Next-Friday.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Naw, baby, no lovin' tonight", "qsentId": 46}]